{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "5 &minus; 10",
      "answer": "-5"
    },
    {
      "question": "-6 + 3",
      "answer": "-3"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + 3",
      "answer": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &minus; -11",
      "answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &minus; -2",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "-5 + -2",
      "answer": "-7"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + -4",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "-3 + 0",
      "answer": "-3"
    },
    {
      "question": "-8 + 3",
      "answer": "-5"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 &minus; -10",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4 + 12",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &minus; -5",
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "-1 + 0",
      "answer": "-1"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &minus; 12",
      "answer": "-6"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &minus; 5",
      "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
      "question": "5 &minus; 0",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &minus; 2",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + -2",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 &minus; -12",
      "answer": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 &minus; -2",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "0 &minus; -12",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2 &minus; 6",
      "answer": "-8"
    },
    {
      "question": "-10 &minus; 3",
      "answer": "-13"
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + -6",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "-12 &minus; 2",
      "answer": "-14"
    },
    {
      "question": "-8 + 1",
      "answer": "-7"
    },
    {
      "question": "-11 &minus; 12",
      "answer": "-23"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 + 9",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 &minus; -11",
      "answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "question": "7 &minus; -3",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &minus; 12",
      "answer": "-3"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4 &minus; 8",
      "answer": "-12"
    },
    {
      "question": "-12 &minus; -10",
      "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 + -9",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &minus; 9",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "11 + 2",
      "answer": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2 + 0",
      "answer": "-2"
    },
    {
      "question": "-6 + 8",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "-10 + 7",
      "answer": "-3"
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + -2",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + -1",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "8 + 7",
      "answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "question": "-4 + -9",
      "answer": "-13"
    },
    {
      "question": "-12 &minus; -8",
      "answer": "-4"
    },
    {
      "question": "11 &minus; -1",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "10 &minus; -8",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "9 &minus; -4",
      "answer": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "-2 + -11",
      "answer": "-13"
    },
    {
      "question": "-6 &minus; 8",
      "answer": "-14"
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 9",
      "answer": "13"
    }
  ]
}
